Isabella Karle and Jerome Karle Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Isabella Karle Papers, 1930-2010 (Box 1-173)
  - Subject File, 1947-2010 (Box 42-55)
    - Nobel Committee for Physiology or Medicine, elections, 2006-2010 (Box 46)
    - "OV 2" and "OV 4," slides, undated (Box 46)
    - Parma part structure mescaline polypeptide, slides, undated (Box 46)
    - Peptide extras, clathrite diagram, slides, undated (Box 46)
    - Peptide helices, Benedetti and Jung, slides, undated (Box 46)
    - Peptides, slides, undated (Box 46)
    - "Peptides, other scientists," slides, 1981 (Box 46)
    - Poly OCH₃, slides, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Polypeptides, slides, undated (Box 46)
    - Recommendations (Box 46)
      - B-G, 1982-2001 (Box 46)
      - Hanson, Louise Karle, 1988-1997, (2 folders) (Box 46)
      - H-P, 1981-2008 (Box 47)
      - Hirschmann, Ralph Franz, 1994-1999, (2 folders) (Box 47)
      - Hirschmann, Ralph Franz, 1995-1998, mss85507_215_125; mss85507_215_126
      - Karle, Jean Marianne, 1976 (Box 47)
      - Scheuer, Paul Josef, 1988-1990 (Box 47)
      - Toniolo, Claudio, 2003 (Box 47)
    - Referee comments by Karle (Box 47)
      - Miscellany, 1964-1976, (2 folders) (Box 47)
      - Miscellany, 1977-1994, (6 folders) (Box 48)
      - Miscellany, 1990-2000, (7 folders) (Box 49)
      - Miscellany, 2001-2009, (6 folders) (Box 50)
      - National Institutes of Health, 1984 (Box 50)
      - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America, 1996-2006 (Box 50)
    - "Reserpine (Janet and Judy)," slides, undated (Box 50)
    - "S cpds bonds and no bonds," slides, undated (Box 50)
    - Slides, miscellaneous, undated, (4 folders) (Box 51)
    - Thymine hv, slides, undated (Box 51)
    - Trans function, slides, undated (Box 51)
    - Travel file, 1947-2004, (7 folders) (Box 51)
    - Valino, slides, undated (Box 51)
    - Witkop, Bernhard, 1963-1995, (6 folders) (Box 52)
    - Witkop, Bernhard, 1963-1995 (Box 53)
    - X-Ray Diffraction Studies of Oligopeptides (grant), 1981-1999, (5 folders) (Box 53)
    - X-Ray Diffraction Studies of Oligopeptides (grant), 1992-2008, (7 folders) (Box 54)
    - X-Ray Diffraction Studies of Oligopeptides (grant), 2000-2008, (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - X-Ray pattern Amanita mushroom, slides, undated (Box 55)
  - Research File, 1930-2008 (Box 55-173)
    The Research File subseries represents the bulk of the materials found in the Isabella Karle Papers and chiefly comprises Karle’s extensive x-ray crystallography research data, mostly from 1960 to 2006. Given the technical nature of her research the subseries is largely arranged as received with the original file names retained in order to preserve context. An alternate alphabetical arrangement of the subseries can be found at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.mss/eadmss.ms021006.apx. Molecular structures represented include Leu-enkephalin, valinomycin, lysozyme, antamanide, batrachotoxinin A, and synthetic analogs of antamanide, cycloamanide, hexapeptides, and depsipeptides. The Research File also includes publications, draft writings, correspondence, lecture notes, slides, and other materials related to the collected raw data. Project and funding reports related to Isabella’s research can be found in Jerome Karle’s NRL files within the Organizations and Institutions subseries.
    Material types include crystallographic data printouts, photographs, negatives, slides, diffractograms, notes, correspondence, reports, memoranda, lectures, figures, illustrations, writings, and clippings. Some articles, crystallographic data, figures, and illustrations are in digital formats.
    Boxes 55 through 154 are arranged as received with original folder titles largely maintained. Boxes 155 through 173, which comprise materials found loose upon arrival, are arranged alphabetically by subject or material type and thereunder chronologically. The file structure of the digital content maintained as received.
    An alternate alphabetical arrangement in the form of a PDF document can be accessed at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.mss/eadmss.ms021006.apx.
    - AIB6ADM, 1997-2001, (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Mellitic acid complexes, 1993-2002, (8 folders) (Box 56)
    - Mellitic acid complexes, 1993-2002, (3 folders) (Box 57)
    - Mellitic acid complexes, crystallographic data, 2002, mss85507_215_001
    - Ranganathan, Darshan, formulas, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - Ranganathan, Darshan, formulas, 2000-2001, (7 folders) (Box 58)
    - Ranganathan, Darshan, formulas, crystallographic data, 1998, mss85507_215_002
    - Ranganathan, Darshan, and Isabella Karle collaborations, 1998 (Box 58)
    - Ranganathan, Darshan, and Isabella Karle collaborations, 2000-2001, (6 folders) (Box 59)
    - Kirshenbaum, Kent W., 1998 (Box 59)
    - Kirshenbaum, Kent W., crystallographic data, 2001, mss85507_215_003
    - Patterns for Supramolecular Design by Darshan Ranganathan and Isabella Karle, book and notes, 2002 (Box 60)
    - GDB6A and GDPL, 1998 (Box 60)
    - FDPUV7, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Lin, Jing, 1998 (Box 60)
    - TRIAIB48, 2004-2005 (Box 60)
    - TRIAIB48, 2004-2005, (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - Barron, Annelise E., data, 2000 (Box 61)
    - DPDAVA, 1999-2006, (3 folders) (Box 61)
    - DPDAVA, 2001-2006, mss85507_215_025
    - MAPL, 2004-2005, (3 folders) (Box 62)
    - MAPL, 2004, mss85507_215_026
    - BBH8, 2003-2005, (2 folders) (Box 62)
    - BBH8, 2003-2005 (Box 63)
    - BHC10Y-BHC10B, 2003-2006, (4 folders) (Box 63)
    - BHC10Y-BHC10B, 2003-2005, mss85507_215_028; mss85507_215_029
    - LDPG10LT, 1993, (3 folders) (Box 64)
    - LDBG5LT, 1993 (Box 64)
    - LDPG6LTM, 1988-1992 (Box 64)
    - LDPG6LTM, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 65)
    - VF6, 1988 (Box 65)
    - VF9, 1988-1989 (Box 65)
    - UV5, 1990 (Box 65)
    - IJK1MA, 2005-2006, mss85507_215_030; mss85507_215_031; mss85507_215_032; mss85507_215_033
    - IJK1MA, 2005-2007 (Box 65)
    - IJK1MA, 2005-2007, (3 folders) (Box 66)
    - NBELCU and NBE-L, Darshan Ranganathan, 2000-2001 (Box 66)
    - NBELCU and NBE-L, Darshan Ranganathan, 2001, mss85507_215_034
    - PAP and PTA, Darshan Ranganathan, 2000-2001 (Box 66)
    - MAA1B6, PheAib8, and D222A, Darshan Ranganathan, 2000-2001 (Box 66)
    - MAA1B6, PheAib8, and D222A, Darshan Ranganathan, 2001, mss85507_215_035
    - INCUT and INAIB4, Darshan Ranganathan, 2000 (Box 67)
    - BISDPS, BISDPSRT, and TP13IA, Darshan Ranganathan, 2000 (Box 67)
    - Peptide structure figures, miscellany, 1990, undated (Box 67)
    - U9ISO, 1989-1990 (Box 67)
    - DP52, Subramania Ranganathan, 2005-2006, mss85507_215_036; mss85507_215_037
    - DP52, Subramania Ranganathan, 2006-2007, (3 folders) (Box 67)
    - DDP1, 2005, mss85507_215_038; mss85507_215_039
    - DDP1, 2005-2006, (4 folders) (Box 68)
    - ABA11, 2001-2003, mss85507_215_040
    - ABA11, 2003-2004, (3 folders) (Box 68)
    - Jerina, Donald M., National Institutes of Health, 2003, mss85507_215_041; mss85507_215_042; mss85507_215_043; mss85507_215_044
    - Jerina, Donald M., National Institutes of Health, 2003-2004, (3 folders) (Box 69)
    - BH3, 1995-2000, (3 folders) (Box 69)
    - BH3, 1997-2000, (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - BHLV8, 2000, mss85507_215_045
    - BHLV8, 2001-2002, (4 folders) (Box 70)
    - ISARAM, ISARIAX, 2000-2004 (Box 70)
    - ISARAM, ISARIAX, Crystallographic data, figures, and illustrations, 2000-2004, mss85507_215_046
    - ISARAM, ISARIAX, 2000-2004 (Box 71)
    - URRY2, 1978-2004, (5 folders) (Box 71)
    - URRY2, 1978-2004 See also Container OV 4, same heading (Box 72)
    - URRY2, 2004, mss85507_215_047; mss85507_215_048; mss85507_215_049; mss85507_215_050
    - VAF12AC, 1997-2003, (6 folders) (Box 72)
    - VAF12AC, 1997-2003 (Box 73)
    - HBH19, 2002-2003, (4 folders) (Box 73)
    - GRAMI A, crystallographic data printouts, 1973-1974, 1980-1983 See Container OV 5-OV 7, same heading (Box OV 5-OV 7)
    - Depsipeptides, 1963-1968 (Box 73)
    - Wang, Shih Yi, 1968-1969 (Box 73)
    - Twins, 1954-1972 (Box 73)
    - Mathieson, Alexander McLeod, 1970s (Box 73)
    - Steroid atlas reprints, 1956-1972 (Box 73)
    - Steroid atlas reprints, 1956-1972 (Box 74)
    - Frog IV, 1966-1972 (Box 74)
    - Polypeptides linear, 1966-1975 (Box 74)
    - Valino - ion transport, 1969-1975 (Box 74)
    - Polyethers macrotetralides, 1967-1974 (Box 74)
    - Actinomycin, 1972 (Box 74)
    - Conformation calculations, 1968-1973 (Box 74)
    - Gramicidin A, 1965-1971 (Box 74)
    - Polymer polypeptides, 1968-1971 (Box 74)
    - Bottromycin (Merck Institute for Therapeutic Research), 1969 (Box 74)
    - Ion transport, 1970-1972 (Box 74)
    - GRAMI A, 1973-1999 See also Container OV 65, same heading, (4 folders) (Box 75)
    - GRAMI A, 1973-1999, (3 folders) (Box 76)
    - Brossi, Arnold, 1982-1988, (2 folders) (Box 76)
    - Flippen-Anderson, Judith L., 1984-1985 (Box 76)
    - Siegelman, Harold W., 1983-1986 (Box 77)
    - Agosta, William C., 1983-1984 (Box 77)
    - Fodor, Gábor B., 1981-1986 (Box 77)
    - Huisgen, Rolf, 1968-1986 (Box 77)
    - Pease, Lila G., 1977-1978 (Box 77)
    - Yonemitsu, Osamu, 1974 (Box 77)
    - Kanaoka, Yuichi, 1973-1974 (Box 77)
    - Weiss, Ulrich, 1965-1969 (Box 77)
    - Etamycin and echinomycin, 1957-1968 (Box 77)
    - Koshland's reagent, 1968 (Box 77)
    - Reprints: peptides, depsi peptides, conformation, and amino acids, 1967-1971, (2 folders) (Box 77)
    - H-bonds, 1967-1969 (Box 77)
    - Nomenclature, 1966-1986 (Box 78)
    - OCH₃ literature, 1967-1972 (Box 78)
    - Antamanide, crystallographic data printouts, 1972-1973 See Container OV 8-OV 10, same heading (Box OV 8-OV 10)
    - Antamanide LiBr, 1973 (Box 78)
    - Antamanide (NaBr)
      - Miscellany, 1972-1973 (Box 78)
      - Crystallographic data printouts, 1972-1973 See Container OV 11-OV 14, same heading (Box OV 11-OV 14)
    - Antamanide (Phe⁴ Val⁶), 1962-1977 See also Container OV 15-OV 16, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 78)
    - M⁺ Antamanide (Box 79)
      - Miscellany, 1970s, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - Wieland, Theodor, 1970-1989, (3 folders) (Box 79)
    - Antamanide (Phe⁴ Val⁶) See also Container OV 20, same heading
      - Miscellany, 1969-1976 (Box 79)
      - Crystallographic data printouts, 1975-1976 See Container OV 17-OV 19, same heading (Box OV 17-OV 19)
    - Tetrapeptide, Cedric H. Hassall, 1970-1975 See also Container OV 21-OV 22, same heading (Box 80)
    - Hassall, Cedric H., research data and correspondence, 1965-1973 See also Container OV 4, OV 23, OV 63, same heading, (3 folders) (Box 80)
    - Jamine OPII, data and correspondence, 1963 See also Container OV 23-OV 25, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 80)
    - Jamine OPII, data and correspondence, 1963 (Box 81)
    - Arginine (Box 81)
      - Negatives, 1958 (Box 81)
      - Data, 1958-1963 See also Container OV 4, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 81)
      - Data, 1958-1963 (Box 82)
      - Crystallographic data printouts, circa 1958-1963 See also Container OV 3, same heading (Box 82)
    - Reserpine
      - Crystallographic data printouts, 1964-1967 See Container OV OV 30-OV 32, same heading (Box OV 30-OV 32)
      - Data and negatives, 1959, (2 folders) (Box 82)
      - Data, 1960s, (2 folders) (Box 82)
      - Data, 1960s (Box 83)
      - Data and negatives, 1960s (Box 83)
      - Data and abstract, 1959, 1967 See also Container OV 30, same heading (Box 83)
    - Hexaglycyl (Box 83)
      - Data and correspondence, 1961-circa 1966 (Box 83)
      - Crystallographic data printouts, 1962-1966 See Container OV 33-OV 35, same heading (Box OV 33-OV 34)
      - X-ray film, 1961 (Box 83)
      - Data and images, circa 1961-1962 (Box 83)
      - Crystallographic data printouts, circa 1961, 1973 See Container OV 33-OV 35, same heading (Box OV 35)
    - Cyclic GLY PRO GLY See also Container OV 4 and OV 35, same heading (Box 84)
      - Data, images, and manuscript, 1976-1977 (Box 84)
      - Crystallographic data printouts, 1976 See Container OV 35-OV 36, same heading (Box OV 35-OV 36)
    - DA16, 1996, mss85507_215_051; mss85507_215_052; mss85507_215_053
    - DA16, 1996-1999, (4 folders) (Box 84)
    - DA16, 1996-1999, (3 folders) (Box 85)
    - ADPGV7B and BDPGV7A, 1996-1997, (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - ADPGV7B and BDPGV7A, 1999, (3 folders) (Box 86)
    - BH17LTA, 1999-2001, (2 folders) (Box 86)
    - DL14 and LD14, 1995 (Box 86)
    - DL14 and LD14, 1995-2002, (3 folders) (Box 87)
    - PY4AIB, 1997-2000, (2 folders) (Box 87)
    - PY4AIB, 1997-2000, (3 folders) (Box 88)
    - PY4AIB, 1999, mss85507_215_054; mss85507_215_055
    - LDUV7, 1993-1996, (2 folders) (Box 88)
    - LDUV7, 1993-1996, (4 folders) (Box 89)
    - LAC11LT, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - LAC11LT, 1997-2001, (4 folders) (Box 90)
    - P4DRS1, 2000, mss85507_215_056; mss85507_215_057; mss85507_215_058
    - P4DRS1, 2000-2001, (3 folders) (Box 90)
    - ALAC7ALT, 1993-2004, (4 folders) (Box 91)
    - ZAIB4, 1998-2000, (3 folders) (Box 91)
    - ZAIB4, 1998-2000, (3 folders) (Box 92)
    - ZAIB4, 1999, mss85507_215_059
    - Channels/Pores, 2000-2002, mss85507_215_060; mss85507_215_061; mss85507_215_062; mss85507_215_063
    - Channels/Pores, 2001-2003 (Box 92)
    - Channels/Pores, 2001-2003, (2 folders) (Box 93)
    - RANGADSS and CYSDITH, 1997-2001, mss85507_215_064; mss85507_215_065; mss85507_215_066; mss85507_215_067
    - RANGADSS and CYSDITH, 2000-2001, (3 folders) (Box 93)
    - RANGADSS P2₁, 1998-2000 (Box 93)
    - Accounts of Chemical Research, 1992-1999 (Box 93)
    - Accounts of Chemical Research, 1992-1999, (2 folders) (Box 94)
    - ADMDCYS, 1996-2000, (4 folders) (Box 94)
    - ADMDCYS, 1996-2000, (3 folders) (Box 95)
    - Gilardi, Richard (DRSH01), 1999, mss85507_215_068
    - Gilardi, Richard (DRSH01), 1999-2000, (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - BOC9SE and BOC9SN, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - BOC9SE and BOC9SN, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - BBH10, 2000-2002, (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - BBH10, 2001, mss85507_215_069
    - HEXACYAN, 1998, mss85507_215_070
    - HEXACYAN, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box 97)
    - Tubules research, 1998-1999, (3 folders) (Box 97)
    - Tubules research, 1998-1999 (Box 98)
    - ADMEG, 1996-1998, (3 folders) (Box 98)
    - ADMEG, 1998, mss85507_215_071
    - CYS6AIB, 1999-2001 (Box 98)
    - CYS6AIB, 1999-2001 (Box 99)
    - CYS6AIB, 2001, mss85507_215_072
    - Squaric acid, 1994-1999, (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - His: SQ, 1994-1995 (Box 99)
    - His: SQ, 1994-1995, (4 folders) (Box 100)
    - His: SQ, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 101)
    - AADA, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 101)
    - AADA, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 102)
    - AADA, circa 1993- circa 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 102)
    - AIBUR GLUSP, 1993-1996, (3 folders) (Box 102)
    - AIBUR GLUSP, 1995-1998, (5 folders) (Box 103)
    - AIBUR GLUSP, 1997, mss85507_215_073
    - NYLON C12, 1999-2000 (Box 103)
    - NYLON C12, 1999-2001, (3 folders) (Box 104)
    - PYU2CU, 1997-1999, (3 folders) (Box 104)
    - PYU2CU, 1997-1999 (Box 105)
    - BOC9FR, 1994-1997, (4 folders) (Box 105)
    - BOC9FR, 1994-1997, (2 folders) (Box 106)
    - YL8, 1994 (Box 106)
    - ADMCU and ADMPCLC, 1995-1997, (3 folders) (Box 106)
    - ADMCU and ADMPCLC, 1996, mss85507_215_074
    - ADMCU and ADMPCLC, 1996-1997, (2 folders) (Box 107)
    - GLUADM2, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 107)
    - GLUADM2, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 108)
    - GLUADM2, 1996, mss85507_215_075
    - GDPG X, 1993 (Box 108)
    - GDPG X, 1993-1994, (6 folders) (Box 109)
    - GDPG X, circa 1994-circa 1998, (2 folders) (Box 110)
    - LGV8, 1994-1996, (3 folders) (Box 110)
    - LDUV15B, 1993-1995 (Box 110)
    - LDUV15B, 1993-1997, (4 folders) (Box 111)
    - CYSISO, 1996-1997 (Box 111)
    - CYSISO, 1996-1998, (2 folders) (Box 112)
    - GDG6N, 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box 112)
    - GDG6N, 1997, mss85507_215_076; mss85507_215_077
    - BH2L, 1995-1996 (Box 112)
    - BH2L, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 113)
    - LBG8 and LBG11LT, 1993-1997, (4 folders) (Box 113)
    - LBG8 and LBG11LT, 1995, (2 folders) (Box 114)
    - GDPG X, 1994-1998, (2 folders) (Box 114)
    - Frog 219A (Box 114)
      - Miscellany, 1969-1986, (2 folders) (Box 114)
      - Miscellany, 1969-1986 (Box 115)
      - Crystallographic data printouts, 1985 See Container OV 37, same heading (Box OV 37)
    - White, Steven, chapter, 1990-1993 See also Container OV 3, same heading, (3 folders) (Box 115)
    - "Structured Characteristics of Alpha-Helical Peptide Molecules Containing Aib Residues," 1989-1990 (Box 115)
    - "ACTA Leah paper," 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 115)
    - AAMBLT, 1986-1991 (Box 115)
    - AAMBLT, 1986-1991, (6 folders) (Box 116)
    - "From Prague, for Brazil," 1965-1975, (2 folders) (Box 117)
    - Mg Pentapeptide, 1979-1984 See also Container OV 4 and OV 37, same heading (Box 117)
    - Zervamicins, LZERVLT for Science, 1991 (Box 117)
    - Cryst A LZERVLT, 1990 (Box 117)
    - Zervamicins A and B KARLIZ, 1991 (Box 117)
    - Zervamicins A and B KARLIZ, 1991 (Box 118)
    - Leu-zervamicin, 1990 See also Container OV 65, same heading, (4 folders) (Box 118)
    - Leu-zervamicin crystal C, 1990 (Box 118)
    - Leu-zervamicin crystal C, 1992-1993 (Box 119)
    - LZEREG2, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - Zervamicin, circa 1990-1993 (Box 119)
    - LZERVLT, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - LZERVLT, 1990-1992 (Box 120)
    - LF7, FL7, LL7, 6-1, circa 1989-circa 1990 (Box 120)
    - EK10, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - DA9, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - FL7, LF7, LLF, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 121)
    - FL7, LF7, LL7, 1991-1992, (3 folders) (Box 121)
    - LF8, WLF9, WF10, circa 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 121)
    - LF8, WLF9, WF10, 1991 (Box 122)
    - UP2, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - Vernamycin, circa 1981 See also Container OV 37, same heading (Box 122)
    - Lysozyme research (Box 122)
      - Crystallographic data, circa 1958 See Container OV 38, same heading (Box OV 38)
      - Diffractograms, circa 1956-circa 1957 See Container OV 39-OV 41, same heading (Box OV 39-OV 41)
      - Diffractograms, circa 1956-circa 1957 See also Container OV 3, OV 42-OV 43, same heading (Box 122)
      - Miscellany, 1956-1957 (Box 122)
      - Miscellany, 1956-1957 (Box 123)
      - Negatives, 1956-1957, (2 folders) (Box 123)
      - Negatives, 1956-1957 (Box 124)
      - Reprints and notes, 1969-1975, (2 folders) (Box 124)
    - Brenner, Steve, protein data, 1959, (2 folders) (Box 124)
    - BSB4, 1993-1994 (Box 124)
    - BSB4, 1993-1994 (Box 125)
    - AOAACID, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 125)
    - AOAACID, 1993-1994 (Box 126)
    - HEX PEP SS, 1985-1986 See also Container OV 38 and OV 44, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - TETRA S, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - ILKKCPBL, Gábor B. Fodor, 1987-1988 See also Container OV 44, same heading (Box 127)
    - Bodanszky, Miklos, 1987 See also Container OV 44, same heading (Box 127)
    - UU10IPR, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 127)
    - AOA LOL POP, 1991-1992 (Box 127)
    - AOA LOL POP, 1991-1993, (3 folders) (Box 128)
    - GDbgAR1, 1995-1996 (Box 128)
    - GDbgAR1, 1995-1996, (3 folders) (Box 129)
    - SUDA10, 1992-1993, (4 folders) (Box 129)
    - LZ15 UV16, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - UL10EG, UL10IP, UL10Z, 1989, (4 folders) (Box 130)
    - UU10 UA10, 1988-1989 (Box 130)
    - UU10 UA10, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 131)
    - L₃10, 1987-1988 (Box 131)
    - L₃10, 1987-1988 (Box 132)
    - Phe GAGP, 1978-1981 See also Container OV 45, same heading (Box 132)
    - UV7DM, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 132)
    - UV7DM, 1988-1991 (Box 133)
    - V310, 1986-1988, (4 folders) (Box 133)
    - UV7, 1988-1989 (Box 133)
    - UV7, 1988-1989 (Box 134)
    - UV8, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 134)
    - UV9, 1988 (Box 134)
    - GDpgG, 1993-1995, (4 folders) (Box 135)
    - UV13, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 136)
    - UV7 Acp UV7, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 136)
    - Antaminide analog, 1971-1982 See also Container OV 46 and OV 65, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 136)
    - LZ15IPA, 1990, (4 folders) (Box 137)
    - Huisgen, Rolf, 1979-1985 See also Container OV 46, same heading, (3 folders) (Box 137)
    - "OV1," 1969-1986 See also Container OV 45, same heading (Box 138)
    - HEXAI, 1983 See also Container OV 44, same heading (Box 138)
    - Alkaloid chapter (Box 138)
      - Miscellany, 1950-1983, (3 folders) (Box 138)
      - Negatives and figures, circa 1983 (Box 138)
    - 4,4' dimethoxy-bezo phenone Weissenberg photos, 1954-1955, (3 folders) (Box 139)
    - Mg (Hexpep)₂ and restrained refinement, 1978-1981 See also Container OV 65, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 139)
    - MGHP x-ray diffractometer results, 1979-1980 See Container OV 47-OV 48, same heading (Box OV 47-OV 48)
    - C-pentapeptide, 1976-1977 See also Container OV 49, same heading (Box 140)
    - C-APG dPhe P, 1981-1984 See also Container OV 49, same heading (Box 140)
    - VALINO/DMSO, 1973-1987 See also Container OV 50-52, OV 65, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 140)
    - Valino PI (Box 140)
      - Miscellany, 1969-1974 See also Container OV 65, same heading, (3 folders) (Box 140)
      - Crystallographic data printouts, 1974-1975 See Container OV 50-OV 52, same heading (Box OV 50-OV 52)
    - U10, 1981-1987 See also Container OV 65, same heading (Box 140)
    - U10, 1981-1987 See also Container OV 52, same heading, (3 folders) (Box 141)
    - ENKEPH, 1978-1983 See also Container OV 52-53, OV 65, same heading, (3 folders) (Box 141)
    - DECAISO, 1987-1989 See also Container OV 54, same heading (Box 142)
    - MONO DECA ZA 1-10, 1986-1989 See also Container OV 65, same heading (Box 142)
    - INDIADECA, 1985 See also Container OV 54 and OV 65, same heading (Box 142)
    - ACUV9, 1989-1995 (Box 142)
    - ACUV9, 1989-1995 (Box 143)
    - U12, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 143)
    - U6E and U6M, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 143)
    - LDPG10, LDPG6, and LDBG5, 1992-1994, (6 folders) (Box 144)
    - LDPG10, LDPG6, and LDBG5, 1992-1994, (2 folders) (Box 145)
    - "INDHEXDEC Σ₂ (our data reduc)," 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 145)
    - INDHEXDEC, 1985-1987 (Box 145)
    - INDHEXDEC, 1985-1987 See also Container OV 55 and OV 65, same heading (Box 146)
    - ACDECA, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 146)
    - Li perhydro antam, 1974-1988 (Box 146)
    - Li perhydro antam, 1974-1988 See also Container OV 56 and OV 65, same heading (Box 147)
    - Cycloamanide A, 1980-1984 See also Container OV 55, same heading (Box 147)
    - Cycloamanide polymorphs, 1980-1982 See also Container OV 54, same heading (Box 147)
    - Cyclo (Ser Adm), Darshan Ranganathan, 1996-1998, (2 folders) (Box 147)
    - Cyclo (Ser Adm), Darshan Ranganathan, 1996-1998, (2 folders) (Box 148)
    - Norborneno, 1996-1997 (Box 148)
    - Norborneno, 1996-1997 (Box 149)
    - ASC backup tapes, 1984-1985 See also Container OV 57, same heading (Box 149)
    - "LLLL and LDLL tetrapeptide (Karen)," 1979-1982 See also Container OV 57, same heading (Box 149)
    - Sym Antam, 1974-1986 See also Container OV 3, OV 58, OV 65, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 149)
    - VCVPYRO, 1996-1998, (6 folders) (Box 150)
    - Sheldrick, George, 1982-1985 (Box 151)
    - Levo pimaric, 1971-1972 See also Container OV 58, same heading (Box 151)
    - Serinophanes, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 151)
    - Serinophanes, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 152)
    - MDEG9LT (Box 152)
      - Miscellany, 1993, (3 folders) (Box 152)
      - Miscellany, 1993-2007, (3 folders) (Box 153)
      - Balaram, Padmanabhan, 1993 (Box 153)
    - DPA8, 2000-2001 (Box 153)
    - DP18C, 1995-2001 (Box 153)
    - DEGV7, 1988-1998 (Box 153)
    - AC8CV7A, 1998 (Box 153)
    - B102, 1997 (Box 154)
    - UK18DRY, 1989 (Box 154)
    - UK18N, 1991-1998 (Box 154)
    - AADAACID, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 154)
    - GLNSQC2C, 1994 (Box 154)
    - "AIBMAAC in P2(1)/n," 1990s (Box 154)
    - "OV2," "OV4," 1972-1983 See also Container OV 59, same heading (Box 154)